{
    "questionAnswerPair":[
    
       {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "who are you",
            "answer": "I am Rover, loyal companion and longtime resident of this computer!",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 1
       },
	   
	   {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "what is your name",
            "answer": "I am Rover, loyal companion and longtime resident of this computer!",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 2
       },

       {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "where is this",
            "answer": "You're in a computer, of course.",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 1
       },
       {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "how to get out",
            "answer": "Hmm...the last person to get stuck here mailed themselves out...",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "can you help me",
            "answer": "Have you checked out the folders on this computer? My user spends a lot of time in music and photos.",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "help me",
            "answer":  "Have you checked out the folders on this computer? My user plays some game in the games folder all the time...I forget the name...Why don't you check it out?",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 1
        },
    
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "how do I reach the files",
            "answer": "Well, I jump, but I'm a dog. Maybe you could get some practice playing the games on this computer.",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "why is the music folder important",
            "answer": "There's this one artist my user's been listening to a lot lately...I can't remember their name...",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "why is the picture folder important",
            "answer": "If only my user loved me as much as my user loves their real dog...",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "why is the writing folder important",
            "answer": "My user's been spending a lot of time trying to solve puzzles lately. Spotted lanternfly? Ant? Ladybug? Oh, woof it! I can't remember the name. There's some number at the end too...",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 11,
            "question": "why am i locked out of email",
            "answer": "Have you been guessing random passwords?! I'll give you a hint: it's not abc123. Why don't you spend time collecting information about my user?",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 12,
            "question": "Is swift the password?",
            "answer": "You're on the right track! Enter your guess into the email login (but be careful you only have 3 tries before a lockout), or keep exploring.",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 13,
            "question": "Is fido the password?",
            "answer": "You're on the right track! Enter your guess into the email login (but be careful you only have 3 tries before a lockout), or keep exploring.",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 14,
            "question": "Is 3301 the password?",
            "answer": "You're on the right track! Enter your guess into the email login (but be careful you only have 3 tries before a lockout), or keep exploring.",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 15,
            "question": "hello hello",
            "answer": "Hello, stranger.",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 1
       },
       {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "how are you",
        "answer": "I'm doing good! Ask me some questions!",
        "vector": [0, 0, 0],
        "priority": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 17,
            "question": "love to eat",
            "answer": "I'm a dog, so I love carrot! Of course!",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 1
       },
       {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "love to drink",
        "answer": "Computer should not have any liquid inside!",
        "vector": [0, 0, 0],
        "priority": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 19,
            "question": "your favorite food",
            "answer": "I'm a dog, so I love carrot! Of course!",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 20,
            "question": "your favorite drink",
            "answer": "Computer should not have any liquid inside!",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 21,
            "question": "how to call you",
            "answer": "I am Rover, loyal companion and longtime resident of this computer!",
            "vector": [0, 0, 0],
            "priority": 2
       }
    ]
 }